你好 朋友
Hello, friend.
"你好 朋友" 這么說太遜了
"Hello, friend." That's lame.
也許我應該給你取一個名字 但是這會讓我們陷入難以解釋的困境
Maybe I should give you a name, but that's a slippery slope.
你只存在于我的腦海中 我們必須得銘記這點
You're only in my head. We have to remember that.
媽的 這種事情真的發生了
Shit. It's actually happened,
我在和一個想象中的人交談
I'm talking to an imaginary person.
我要告訴你的是最高機密
What I'm about to tell you is top secret,
一個超乎我們所有人意想的陰謀
a conspiracy bigger than all of us.
在此之外 有一群極富權勢的人
There's a powerful groupof people out there
在秘密地操控著這個世界
that are secretly running the world.
沒有人知道他們我所說的這些人
I'm talking about the guys no one knows about,
這些家伙是無處可見的
the guys that are invisible.
他們是頂尖的那1%人中的1%
The top 1% of the top 1%,
不需要誰允許 他們就能扮演上帝
the guys that play God without permission.
而現在我覺得他們在跟蹤我
And now I think they're following me.
這些都和昨晚有關
This is about last night.
我本應該去安吉拉的生日派對
I should've gone to Angela's birthday party.
相反 我去了--
Instead, I went to--
嗨 羅恩
Hey, Ron.
給
There you go.
你是羅恩
You're Ron.
但是你的真名是羅希特 每塔
But your real name is Rohit Mehta.
你把它改成了羅恩 就在你六年前
You changed it to Ron when you bought
買下你的第一家羅恩的咖啡店的時候
your first Ron's Coffee Shop six years ago.
現在你有了17家分店 下一季度還會開8家新店
Now you got 17 of 'em,with 8 more coming next quarter.
我能幫你做些什么嗎?
May I help you with something?
我喜歡來這兒 因為你這兒的無線網很快
I like coming here 'cause your Wi-Fi was fast.
我的意思是 你這兒是為數不多的幾個
I mean, you're one of the few spots
用光纖連接 能達到千兆位速度的地方之一
that has a fiber connection with gigabit speed.
這很好 特別好 它觸動了
It's good. So good, it scratched
我心里的一部分 那一部分關于好的事情
that part of my mind, part that doesn't allow good to exist
不該無緣無故出現的想法 所以我開始攔截
without condition,so I started intercepting
你網絡中的所有通信量
all the traffic on your network.
這時候我注意到有些蹊蹺
That's when I noticed something strange.
也就是那個時候我決定黑了你
It's when I decided to hack you.
- 黑了--
- Hack--
我知道你在經營一個叫"柏拉圖的男孩"的網站
-I know you run a website called Plato's Boys.
不好意思?
- Pardon me?
你在用洋蔥路由網絡
You're using Tor networking
來使你的服務器保持匿名
to keep the servers anonymous.
你為了不讓別人看到 確實在這兒費了一番功夫
You made it really hard for anyone to see it,
但是我看到了
but I saw it.
洋蔥路由協定
The onion routing protocol,
并沒有你想象中的那么能隱姓埋名
it's not as anonymous  as you think it is.
不論是誰 只要被已存在的節點管理
Whoever's in control of the exit nodes
也會被網絡通信所掌握
is also in control of the traffic,
這也就讓我成為... 能夠掌控這些的人
which makes me... the one in control.
我必須禮貌地請你離開
I must ask you to kindly leave.
我掌握了一切
I own everything.
你所有的郵件 你所有的文檔
All your emails. All your files.
你所有的...圖片
All your...pics.
馬上從這兒滾出去 否則我要叫...
Get out of here right now, or I'll call the--
警察? 你希望他們發現
Police? You want them to find out
你提供給你的40萬用戶的那些超過
about the 100 terabytes of child pornography
100千兆字節的兒童色情片么?
you serve to your 400,000 users?
就我個人來說 哥們兒 我會希望這不過是些
Personally, man, I was hoping it was just gonna be
捆綁性虐一類的東西
some BDSM stuff.
你知道那樣 事情會簡單多少么?
You realize how much simpler that would have been?
我沒有傷害任何人
I did not hurt anyone.
我從沒傷害過
I never did.
那是我的... 個人生活
That's my... personal life.
我很理解和別人不一樣
I understand what it's like
是什么感覺
to be different.
我也很不一樣
I'm very different too.
我的意思是 我不會對著小孩手淫 只不過...
I mean, I don't jerk off to little kids, but...
我不懂得如何和人交流
I don't know how to talk to people.
我爸爸是我唯一能夠進行交流的人
My dad was the only one I could talk to.
但是他死了
But he died.
我很抱歉聽到這個消息
I'm sorry to hear that.
我能問問
How did he pass,
他是怎么死的么?
may I ask?
白血病
Leukemia.
他得病毫無疑問是因為他工作的
He definitely got it from radiation
公司里的那些輻射
at the company he worked at,
雖然我沒有辦法證明這一點
though I couldn't prove it.
現在他死了
Now he's dead.
不過公司還好好的
Company's fine, though.
哦... 嘿
Oh...hey.
沒關系 羅希特
It's okay, Rohit.
你不需要擔心了
You don't have to worry anymore.
我沒聽懂
I don't understand.
你是在敲詐我么?
Are you blackmailing me?
所以這一切都是關于...
So that's what this is about...
錢
money.
這就是你想要的 哈?
That's all you care about, huh?
不行
No.
如果我現在付錢給你 你就會越要越多
If I pay you now,you'll want more and more.
無論我給你多少
No matter how much I give.
你都會告訴警察的
You will inform the police anyway.
我不會付錢給你的 先生
I won't pay you, sir.
記住 你也違反了法律
Remember, you also broke the law.
事實上 你講對了
Actually, you're right.
只講對了一部分
Partly.
是這樣 我通常是在我的電腦上
See, I usually do this kind of thing
做這些事情
from my computer,
但是這次我想脫離電腦來做
but this time I wanted to do it  AFK.
親自當面做
In person.
努力來克服我的社交焦慮
Trying to work on my social anxiety.
不過在我把你叫出來以后 總是會有
But there's always the threat of you fleeing
你會逃跑的威脅存在
after I call you out.
你會告訴你的系統管理員
You'd tell your sys admin
關閉你的服務器 抹掉所有數據
to take your servers down,wipe all the data.
所以我保證
So I made sure to include
我的匿名舉報中 會包含現在的時間
the current time and location
還有地點
on my anonymous tip.
等一下 別走
Wait. Hold on.
我給你錢
I'll give you the money.
我付你錢
I'll pay you.
你想要多少?
How much do you want?
我付你錢
I'll pay you.
你想要多少?
How much do you want?
我都會給你
I'll pay you.
這就是你想錯的那部分 羅希特
That's the part you were wrong about, Rohit.
我才不在乎什么鳥錢
I don't give a shit about money.
機器人先生
第一季  第一集
現在我被跟蹤了
Now I'm being followed.
高層的人不喜歡有我這樣能力的人
The higher ups don't like someone with my powers.
在短短的三分鐘里
In three short minutes,
我毀掉了一個男人的事業 生活和存在
I destroyed a man's business,life, existence.
我刪除了他
- I deleted him.
嘿!
- Hey!
嘿 你
Hey, you.
嘿 小孩兒
Hey, kiddo.
發生什么了?
What's happening?
現在正是這個世界上激動人心的時期
Exciting time in the world right now.
激動人心的時期
Exciting time.
可是我只是一個黑夜里維護秩序的黑客
But I'm only a vigilante hacker by night.
在白天 不過是一個普通的
By day, just a regular
網絡安全工程師
cyber security engineer,
員工編號 ER28-0652
employee number ER28-0652.
伊利艾特!
Elliot!
這兒
In here.
怎么了?
- What's up?
伊爾
- El.
好了 我完全能 我完全能搞定這個
Yeah, I can totally-- I can totally handle it.
他們又被黑了了
They were hacked again.
昨天晚上
Last night.
吉迪恩...
Gideon...
那個是我的發小安吉拉
That's my childhood friend Angela.
她有時候會神經兮兮的
She can be a bit high strung sometimes,
但是相信我 她是好人一個
but trust me-- she's one of the good ones.
我看的這是什么?
What am I looking at?
是訪客記錄文檔么?
Is this the log file?
這是一次RUDY攻擊
This was a RUDY attack.
真是太棒了
This is awesome.
吉迪恩 你能不能回答我?
- Gideon, will you answer me?
太棒了?
- Awesome?
你覺得這很棒? 這會弄死我們的 伊利艾特
You think this is awesome? This is killing us, Elliot.
- 吉迪恩 我不是 - 安吉拉!
- Gideon, I'm not-- - Angela!
我們還是看看今天這個會怎么開吧
Let's just see how this meeting goes today.
他們的網絡每周都會遭到攻擊
Their networks are getting attacked every week.
誰知道他們會不會愿意繼續做我們的顧客
Who knows if they'll still even be a client.
他們黑進來了? 嘿 我們是怎么說的
They're coming in? Hey, what did we say
員工著裝要求?
about the dress code?
好吧 現在看完那些記錄
All right, now,look over those logs.
然后下午要準備好以防他們有任何問題
And be ready this afternoon in case they have any questions.
好么?
Okay?
好的
Okay.
- 又開始抽煙了? - 你昨天晚上
- Start smoking again? - Did you not get
是不是沒收到我的短信?
my texts last night?
我實打實地給你發了13條
I sent you exactly 13 of them.
啊 我很抱歉
Yeah, I'm sorry.
我沒能去成
I couldn't make it.
你答應過我
You promised me that you were
你這次會試試的
gonna try this time.
當我和你說話的時候
Stop thinking about something else
不要想別的事情
when I'm talking to you.
我討厭你那么做
I hate when you do that.
對不起 我是在想工作的事情
Sorry. I was thinking about work.
也許這就是為什么吉迪恩這么愛你的原因吧
Maybe that's why Gideon oves you so much.
他一直感謝我引薦了你
He thanks me all the time for bringing you in.
但是不知道為什么
But for some reason,
我覺得你私下里很討厭這兒
I think you secretly hate it here.
她說對了
She was right.
我更喜歡這兒的人
I liked most of the people,
而不是我們保護大集團的
but our business, a cyber security firm
網絡安全公司的這份工作
that protects corporations--
我想不出比這更討厭的事情了
I can't think of anything I hate more.
不是啊 我喜歡這兒
No, I love it here.
不好意思
I'm sorry.
我只是心情不大好
I'm just in a bad mood.
我已經拖延支付了
I'm late on my last
最近的兩筆助學貸款還款
two student loan payments,
我也不能讓吉迪恩給我加薪
and I can't get Gideon to give me a raise.
呦 哥們兒
Yo, buddy.
昨晚上沒見你
Missed you last night.
你去哪了?
Where were you?
我走了
Gotta go.
今天的會很重要
Big meeting today.
你搞明白發生什么了嗎?
Did you find out what happened?
嗯 他說他在工作
Yeah. He said he was working.
哦 得了吧
Oh, come on.
你得和他談談
You gotta talk to him.
我們要在員工大會上遲到了
We're gonna be late for the staff meeting.
他根本就受不了我
He can't stand me.
而你知道為什么
And you know why.
安吉拉 我不能夠
Angela, I can't have
讓我的生活中有那樣的負能量
that kind of negativity in my life.
這才是我要說的
That's exactly what I'm talking about.
你在想什么啊?
What are you thinking about?
沒什么
Nothing.
你想知道 我在想什么嗎?
You want to know what I'm thinking about?
你第一次來找我的時候
First time you came to me.
準確說我并不是去找克里斯塔
I didn't exactly come to Krista.
我是被逼去的
I was forced here.
不過我的確喜歡她
But I do like her.
黑她的電腦很容易
Hacking her was simple.
她的密碼是 Dylan 2791
Her password: Dylan 2791.
最欣賞的藝術家和
Favorite artist and the year in
她出生的年份倒過來
which she was born, backwards.
雖然她是個心理醫生
Though she's a psychologist,
但她讀人的能力
she's really bad
實在是差勁
at reading people.
不過我很擅長讀人
But I'm good at reading people.
我看得到
I look for
他們最糟糕的一面
the worst in them.
我知道她四年前
I know she went through
經歷了一次離婚
a divorce four years ago.
我知道她曾因此精神崩潰
I know she was devastated by it
還從那后在百合網上
and has been dating losers
和些窩囊廢約會
on eHarmony ever since.
她最近的囊中物是--
Her most recent foray--
邁克爾 漢森
Michael Hansen.
我在網上搜索了他 但是一無所獲
I searched for him online,but nothing came up.
沒有領英網資料 沒有臉書 干干凈凈
No LinkedIn, no Facebook,nothing.
他的一些事情困擾著我
Something about him bugs me,
又一次觸動了我心里的一部分
scratching that part  of my mind again.
但是我很快就能黑他了 我總能黑別人
But I'll hack him soon enough.I always do.
我知道你已經不像以前那樣大喊大叫了
I know you're not yelling like before,
這很好
which is good.
但是我能察覺到你還是不能釋懷
But I can tell you're still holding on to it.
我們需要解決你的暴躁易怒 伊利艾特
And we need to work on your anger issues, Elliot.
你對每個人 對社會都心懷憤恨...
You're angry at everyone, at society...
操你媽的社會
Fuck society.
我知道你有很多可憤怒的事情
I know you have a lot to be angry about,
但是要壓制在自己內心里 保持冷靜
but keeping it to yourself and staying quiet
像你現在這樣這樣是對你自己沒有幫助的
like you're doing--it's not going to help you.
在表象下的痛苦
There's pain underneath.
這才是我們需要解決的問題
That's where our work needs to go.
這個社會怎么讓你這么不滿呢?
What is it about society that disappoints you so much?
哦 我不知道
Oh, I don't know.
是因為我們都覺得史蒂夫 喬布斯
Is it that we collectively thought Steve Jobs
是個偉大的人 即使是我們都知道
was a great man, even when we knew
他的數十億資產是因為童工才得以成功?
he made billions off the backs of children?
或者是因為似乎我們所有的英雄偶像都是偽君子
Or maybe it's that it feels like all our heroesare counterfeit.
世界本身就是一個巨大的騙局
The world itself's just one big hoax.
發各種狗屁實況轉播的垃圾郵件
Spamming with our running commentary of bullshit
偽裝自己的內心 我們的社交媒體都在假裝親密
masquerading as insight, our social media faking as intimacy.
還是我們自己選擇了這些?
Or is it that we voted for this?
不是通過作弊選舉 而是通過我們自己的東西
Not with our rigged elections,but with our things,
自己的財產 自己的錢財
our property, our money.
我所講的都不是新聞
I'm not saying anything new.
我們都知道自己為什么這么做
We all know why we do this,
不是因為饑餓游戲的書籍讓我們覺得開心
not because Hunger Games books makes us happy
是因為我們想要沉著下來
but because we wanna be sedated.
因為這份苦痛不用假裝
Because it's painful not to pretend,
因為我們都是膽小鬼
because we're cowards.
操你媽的社會
Fuck society.
伊利艾特 伊利艾特
Elliot. Elliot.
你什么也不說
You're not saying anything.
這是怎么了?
What's wrong?
沒什么
Nothing.
別泄氣
Don't be frustrated.
我為什么不應該泄氣
Why shouldn't I be?
你和大多數人都不一樣
You're different than most.
至少你努力了
You at least try.
至少你懂得了
You at least understand.
懂什么了?
Understand what?
孤獨的滋味
What it's like to feel alone.
你懂得這種苦痛
You understand the pain.
你想要保護人們遠離苦痛
You want to protect people from it.
你想要保護我遠離苦痛
You want to protect me from it.
我敬重你這一點
I respect that about you.
你為什么覺得我懂得孤獨的滋味?
Why do you think I know what it's like to feel alone?
媽的! 從她的郵件知道的!
Shit! From her emails!
伊利艾特?
Elliot?
我也不知道
I don't know.
我們來說說昨天晚上
Let's talk about last night.
你去安吉拉的生日派對了嗎?
Did you go to Angela's birthday party?
去了 辦的不錯
Yeah. It was nice.
你有沒有試著和什么人講話?
Did you try to talk to anyone?
當然
Sure.
我要到了一個女孩的號碼
I got a girl's number.
你要到了號碼?
You did?
她很漂亮
She's cute.
她很喜歡饑餓游戲
She likes The Hunger Games.
你又在隱藏自己了 伊利艾特
You're hiding again, Elliot.
你隱藏自己的時候 你的錯覺就又出來了
When you hide, your delusions come back.
這是一種滑坡效應
It's a slippery slope.
我們來講講你一直能看到的那些黑衣人
Let's talk about the men in black you've been seeing.
他們還在那嗎?
Are they still there?
沒有了 我 告訴你他們都消失了
No, I... told you they're gone.
你給我的藥起作用了
The meds you gave me are working.
喲 老兄
Yo, man.
你想要 額...
Do you wanna, uh...
你想要今天一起吃午飯嗎?
you wanna do lunch today?
額 恩...
Uh, yeah...
-我有約了 -有約了 對啊
-I got other plans.-Other plans. Right.
前... 前三次我問你的時候你也是這么說的
That's...what you said the last three times I asked you.
聽著 老兄 你....
Look, bud, you...
和安吉拉一直以來都很親近
and Angela have been close
這是我想要和你搞好關系的更為重要的理由
for a long time, and that's even more reason why I want us to be on good terms.
我 我就是 就是覺得我們兩個之間有點尷尬
I-I just--I feel like things have been awkward between us.
你不覺得嗎?
Don't you?
我覺得我們兩個之間尷尬沒所謂
I'm okay with it being awkward between us.
額 好吧
Um, yeah.
我 我 我覺得這樣有所謂
I-I'm--I'm not okay with that.
額.. 聽著 老兄 我愛安吉拉
Um...look, man, I love Angela,
我想我們兩個看在她的份上好好相處
and I want us to-- to get along for her sake.
我的意思是 這是我 這是我此時此刻在這的原因
I mean, that's what I'm-- that's what I'm here for.
我就是 我通常不做這樣的...
I just, I... I don't normally do stuff...
我不喜歡這個人太神經質了嗎?
Am I crazy not to like this guy?
他的臉書點贊的有
Among some of his Facebook likes
喬治W布什的 決策時刻
are George W. Bush's Decision Points,
變形金剛2: 卷土重來
Transformers 2: Revenge of the Fallen,
喬詩葛洛班的音樂
and the music of Josh Groban.
我還要更進一步證明我的想法?
Must I really justify myself any further?
我還在攻克這些狗鋪 你知道嗎?
I'm working on that shit, you know?
他是最容易黑的人 密碼是123456七
His was the easiest to hack. Password was 123456Seven.
我見證了他通過微信對安吉拉說的第一句"我愛你"
I witnessed his first "I love you" With Angela over Gchat,
接著我又見證了第一次偷偷與史黛拉B出軌
then I witnessed the first of many infidelities with Stella B.
我從來沒有做過這樣的事...我想過要告訴安吉拉
I've never done anything like this before...I've thought about telling Angela,
但是她對男人的品位跟屎一樣
but she has shitty taste in men,
而且我也沒有準備好看看接下來會發生什么
and I'm not quite ready to see what comes after this just yet.
你喜歡音樂 我喜歡音樂
You like music. I like music.
魔力紅
Maroon 5.
而且奧利比起其他人更容易被我控制
Plus I can manage Ollie easier than the others.
不管怎么說 至少現在是這樣
for now, anyway.
我就是這個意思
And that's all I mean.
我就是想要你知道
I just want you to know that.
我喜歡你 兄弟 而且...
I like you, bro, and...
我也想要你喜歡我
I want you to like me too.
我理解
I understand.
我會更加努力的
I'll try harder.
沒關系的 老兄
That's cool, man.
嘿 不管你什么時候準備好了 我都愿意...
Hey, whenever you're ready, I'd love to just...
被你震一下
chill.
哦 忘了你 不愿意被人碰
Oh--forgot about your... no touching thing.
事實上 我不應該討厭奧利 他不是個很壞的人
Truth is, I shouldn't hate Ollie; he's not that bad a guy.
他太蠢不夠格當壞人
He's too dumb to be bad.
事實上 當我想到非常壞的人...
In fact, when I think about the really bad people...
E公司 世界上最大的綜合企業
E Corp, the largest conglomerate in the world...
企業之大
they're so big,
他們真的是無處不在
they're literally everywhere.
真是現代社會最完美的妖魔
A perfect monster of modern society.
-E可能是代表邪惡 -所有的生命所需
-The E might as well stand for Evil. -And all of life's necessities...
事實上 經過一番徹底的精密的自我編程
In fact, after a thorough,intensive self-reprogramming,
這就是我所聽到 看到 讀到的
that's all my mind hears, sees, or reads
-當他們突然出現在我的世界里 -這就是必須要提供的
-when they pop up in my world. -That was have to offer.
眾志成城 我們就能改變世界
Together, we can change the world,
E- 邪惡公司
with E-- Evil Corp.
如果克里斯塔知道我這么做肯定會被嚇得不輕
Krista would have a shit fit if she knew I did that.
但是這就是他們的本質 一家邪惡大企業
But that's what they are-- a conglomerate of evil.
現在我不得不幫助他們
And now I have to help them.
負責您公司的有6位在線工程師
There are six on-site engineers on your account.
- 加上幾位線下... - 就是他 泰利 科爾比  首席技術官
- Plus a few off-site...- There he is, Terry Colby,the CTO.
雖然他是世界上最大公司之一的技術人員頭目
Even though he's the head technology guy at one of the biggest companies in the world,
他還是用黑莓
he owns a Blackberry.
所以目前為止就是這樣
So this is it right here.
而且看起來好像他不經常用電腦
But also looks like he doesn't see a terminal very often
他不是個技術專家 他是個腦殘
He's not a techie. He's a moron.
一個傲慢的腦殘
An arrogant moron.
最差勁的那種
The worst kind.
哦 嗨 我是提瑞爾 威力克
Oh, hi. Tyrell Wellick.
我是科技部高級副總裁
I'm Senior Vice President, Technology.
伊利艾特 我就是個技術工
Elliot. Just a tech.
別這么謙虛
Don't be so humble.
要知道 我也是從你這個位子起家的
You know, I started out exactly where you are,
而且 實話說 你知道的 我的心還在這里呢
and...to be honest, you know,my heart is still there.
我看你在運行Gnome啊
So I see you're running Gnome.
你知道 我自己其實還在用KDE
You know, I'm actually on KDE myself.
我知道你的這個桌面環境應該更完善的 但是
I know this desktop environment is supposed to be better but...
你也知道他們怎么說
you know what they say.
舊習難改
Old habits-- they die hard.
一個行政人員運行Linux
An executive running Linux with--
恩 我知道你在想什么
Yeah, I know what you're thinking.
我是個行政人員 我是說
I'm an executive. I mean...
我為什么要運行Linux呢?
why am I even running Linux?
再說一遍 是因為舊習
Again--old habits.
和你一起工作肯定很有趣
It's gonna be fun working with you.
我該去找我的團隊了
I should join the rest of the group.
再見 伊利艾特
Bonsoir, Elliot.
有時候我夢想拯救世界
Sometimes I dream of saving the world.
拯救每個人逃脫無形的手
Saving everyone from the invisible hand,
那只用員工證歸類我們的手
one that brands us with an employee badge.
那只迫使我們為他們工作的手
The one that forces us to work for them...
那只每天控制著我們而我們卻不自知的手
The one that controls us every day without us knowing it.
但是我無法阻止它
But I can't stop it.
我并不那樣特殊
I'm not that special.
我只是個無名小卒
I'm just anonymous.
我踽踽獨行
I'm just alone.
如果不是為了庫爾提
If it weren't for Qwerty,
我會變得徹底空虛
I'd be completely empty.
我恨我難抑內心空虛的時候
I hate when I can't hold in my loneliness.
哭泣得太頻繁
This crying has been happening too often,
現在每隔一周發作一次
every other week now.
當正常的人這樣難過的時候都做什么?
What do normal people do when they get this sad?
他們聯系朋友或家人 我是這么覺得的
They reach out to friends or family, I think.
我沒有這種選擇
That's not an option.
我只能嗑嗎啡
I do morphine.
嗑嗎啡而又不會把自己變成癮君子的關鍵在于
The key to doing morphine without turning into a junkie
每天限食30毫克
is to limit yourself to 30 milligrams a day.
再多的吸食就會產生藥物耐受性
Anything more just builds up your tolerance.
我核查了每片藥的純度
I check every pill I get for purity.
我有8毫克的納洛酮以維持
I have 8 milligram Suboxone for maintenance
以防我退癮
in case I go through withdrawals.
媽的! 我又用完了
Shit! I'm out again.
多少錢？
How much?
我請了
On the house.
不 夏拉
No, Shayla.
別這樣
Not doing that.
好嗎? 這只是一個
Okay? This is just
普通的毒品交易
a regular drug deal
就像我們之前做的
like it always is.
好吧
Fine.
所以你今晚要做什么?
So what are you up to tonight?
我嘗試在
'Cause I tried to post
你的臉書上發點東西
something on your Facebook
但是我沒有找到你
and couldn't find you.
我沒有臉書賬號
I'm not on Facebook.
什么? 為啥?
What? Why not?
因為我討厭臉書
'Cause I hate Facebook.
這太不正常了
That's crazy.
那你今晚想不想
Well...you want to
一起吸點這個?
do these together then?
純搖頭丸哦...
Pure Molly...
永遠不要在你嗑藥之后做決定
Don't ever make decisions when you're on morphine.
Instagram上顯示克里斯塔
Instagram check-in
去了綠蒂酒吧
for Krista at Pierre Loti.
好的 邁克爾 漢森
Okay, Michael Hansen.
是時候該查明你到底是誰了
Time to find out who you really are.
謝謝你 再見
Thank you. Bye.
出租車!
Taxi!
喂 你好 我剛剛把
Uh, hi--I just left
我的鑰匙落在你們的出租車上了
my keys in one of your cabs.
56Y2
56Y2.
好的
Sure.
你們兩個怎么說?
What about you two?
你們有沒有
You guys got any
多余的零錢?
spare change?
來幫我解決溫飽問題？
Help me out?
紐約人都很有錢的 朋友們
New York's expensive, guys.
施舍一點吧
Come on.
霍桑街306號
306 Hawthorne.
謝謝你 非常感謝你
Thank you.Thank you.
快點 笨蛋
Come on, asshole
已經噓噓過了
Piss already.
快點
Come on!
快點啊你
你...你不想走嗎？
Will you--will you go?
快點 我們走啊 走 你不是要走嗎？
Come on, go, go! Go, will ya?
嘿
Hey.
我可以借一下你的手機嗎?
May I borrow your phone?
我的沒電了
Mine's dead.
我需要給我媽媽打個電話
I need to call my mom.
謝謝你了
Thank you.
沒人接
No answer.
還是謝謝你了
Thanks anyway.
安吉拉 有事嗎?
Angela,is everything okay?
我需要你來公司一下
I need you to come to AllSafe.
你在那?
You're there?
現在可是凌晨三點
It's 3:00 in the morning.
他們又一次攻擊了邪惡公司
They attacked Evil Corp
的服務器
servers again,
這次要嚴重的多
but it's bad this time.
這次是分布式拒絕服務攻擊
It's a DDoS attack.
你給羅伊德打電話了嗎? 現在該他值班
Did you call Lloyd? He's on call.
對 他現在在這里
Yeah, he's here.
他跟公司的技術部門聯系過了嗎?
Is he talking to their tech department?
他現在在跟他們線上交流
He's online with them,
但是目前一無所獲
but so far nothing.
我不覺得
I don't think that
羅伊德能夠解決這個問題
Lloyd can handle this.
聽著 吉迪恩剛剛把我調到這里來
Look, Gideon just put me on this account.
我不能才工作一周
I can't screw up
就把事情搞砸了
in my first week.
我需要你
I need you.
拜托了
Please.
防火墻進入受阻可能的分布式拒絕服務攻擊[拒絕連接]
我馬上過去
I'll be right there.
終于來了
Finally!
冷靜 這才一個小時
Calm down it's only been an hour.
當然 一個小時對邪惡公司來說可是大約1300萬美元的收入
Yeah, well, an hour in Evil Corp time is like $13 million in revenue, approximately.
實際上
Actually,
我計算過了
I calculated that.
這就是他們損失的錢數
That's exactly how much they lost.
不要擔心
Don't worry.
我來幫你了
I got you.
羅伊德 怎么樣了?
Lloyd, what's up?
羅伊德!
Lloyd!
伊利艾特 情況很糟糕
Elliot. This is bad.
這是我見過的最棘手的分布式拒絕服務攻擊
Worst DDoS attack I've ever seen.
你能夠重新辨別域名嗎?
Did you reconfigure the DNS?
可以
Yes!
終止服務
Stop the services.
我已經終止了所有的服務 現在在嘗試重啟服務器
I already stopped the services, tries to reboot the servers
但是現在不能夠啟動服務器了
but they're not coming back up.
伙計 現在有人正在著手攻擊他們的整個網絡 就在現在
Dude, someone is straight up fingerblasting their entire network right now.
已經有相關報道了
They just started reporting on the outage.
有消息稱公司網絡服務器遭黑客攻擊比之前預估嚴重
該死 這比我想的還要糟
Shit. This is worse than I thought.
他們現在在網上?
They're in the network?
現在是什么情況?
What's the status update?
我以為我們有設置網絡安全協議呢
I thought we set up security protocols
所以這個不會發生
so that this doesn't happen.
這個攻擊源自哪里?
Where's the attack coming from?
很顯然 是從各個地方
Everywhere, obviously.
美國 芬蘭 泰國 科威特
The USA, Finland, Thailand, Kuwait--
開始重啟所有的服務器 開始共享 重定所有的數據流量 叫Prolexic幫忙
Start restarting the services, load sharing, redirect the traffic. Call Prolexic for help.
Prolexic是一家美國的云安全解決方案提供商 現被Akamai收購
怎么了?
What?
我不覺得這只是一次分布式拒絕服務攻擊那么簡單
I don't think this is just a DDoS attack.
我覺得他們已經獲得了一個隱匿程式 現在已經侵入到了整個服務器中了
I think they got a rootkit sitting inside the servers.
什么是隱匿程式?
What's a rootkit?
它就像是一個有著大屌的瘋狂強奸慣犯
It's like a crazy serial rapist with a very big dick.
上帝啊 羅伊德
Jesus, Lloyd.
對不起 就是能使系統徹底癱瘓的惡意代碼
Sorry. It's malicious code that completely takes over their system.
它能夠刪除系統文件
It can delete system files
終止所有的程序
and stop programs.
病毒 蠕蟲病毒
Viruses, worms
我們怎么才能阻止它?
How do we stop it?
這就是問題所在
That's the thing.
這個完全是隱形的 你無法阻止它
It's fundamentally invisible you can't stop it.
他們所有的服務器都已經超時了
All of their servers are timing out.
沒有辦法進行重啟
None of them are coming back up.
這是因為每次我們重新啟動服務器 病毒就會在這時候啟動
That's because every time we restart the server the virus replicates itself
加倍 從而破壞主機
during boot up and crashes the host.
所以我們怎樣才能救活整個網絡 如果我們不能重啟整個服務器?
How are we supposed to bring up the network if we can't restart the servers?
我們不能
We can't.
這就是他們想要的
Which is what they wanted.
通過保護自己 我們最后會將將病毒擴散到每個地方
By defending ourselves, we ended up spreading the virus everywhere.
我們能做的就是把整個系統斷開連接
Only thing we can do is we've gotta take the whole system offline
然后格式化被感染的服務器 清理干凈 然后再將其重啟備份
wipe the infected servers, clean, then bring them back up.
你跟我來
You're coming with me.
好
Yeah.
羅伊德
Lloyd.
好
Yeah.
羅伊德
Lloyd.
告訴所有人開始把所有的服務器斷開連接
Tell everybody to start taking everything offline.
在做了
On it.
服務器都在杜勒斯 我們需要一架飛機
Uh, the server farm in Dulles. We're gonna need the jet.
他們正在啟動服務器的備份
They're booting the network back up.
你現在開始下載所有的日志信息 對
Now, you're downloading the logs, right--
停 告訴他停下來
Stop. Tell him to stop.
怎么了?
What?
不要開始啟動序列
Don't start the boot sequence.
你們漏了一個
You guys missed one.
這里還有一個在運行的被感染的服務器
There's an infected server up and running.
在它攻擊這個服務器前我們還有多少時間?
What's the ETA before it hits this server?
備份服務器已經開始運行了?
The backup server up and running?
它準備好了 但是并沒有開始配置自動開關
It's ready, but it's not configured for auto switch.
我們需要重新定向所有的數據 然后改變域名
We need to redirect the traffic, need to switch DNS.
沒問題的 你搞定的 你能做到的
you got this. You got this, you got this,
這不現實啊
This is impossible.
能做到的 能做到的 你能做到的
you got this, you got this. You got this,
它馬上就到備份服務器了
It's almost at the back server!
我們還在線上?
We still up?
我們沒事了
We're okay.
是啊
Yeah.
漢克
Hank.
我現在要看一下受感染的服務器  給我點時間 行嗎?
I'm gonna take a look at the infected server, okay?  Give me a minute
恩 我在電梯里等著你
Yeah. Uh...I'll meet you at the elevators.
他們一定會留下一些痕跡
They must have left a mark or something.
每個黑客都渴望被關注
Every hacker loves attention.
他們才不會沒有原因的用分布式拒絕服務攻擊
They don't just do DDoS attacks for no reason.
這就是了
This is it.
F社會
Fsociety.
這難道是一個笑話?
Is that supposed to be a joke?
這實在是有點太簡單了 他們并沒有隱藏什么
This was way too easy. They didn't hide it well at all.
留著我
這是給我的
This note is for me.
他們在告訴我 讓我把它留下來
They're telling me to leave it here.
但是為什么? 這不重要
But why? Doesn't matter.
我們該關掉這些了
Time to shut them down.
為什么我不能刪除它?
Why can't I delete it?
我不想要去刪除它 我想要它呆在那里
I don't want to delete it. I want it to stay.
我這是怎么了?
What's wrong with me?
我將會重新配置根目錄的授權 這樣只有我才能使用
I'll reconfigure the access to the root directory so only I can use it.
沒人會知道
And no one will know.
給您的 先生
For you, sir.
你知道其實我是同性戀嗎?
Did you know that I'm gay?
不
No.
把這個當成是我對你出柜了 好吧?
Consider this me coming out to you then, okay?
這有點難 因為我不想談論我的性生活
It's hard because I don't like to talk about my sex life.
但是我的伴侶 他疑心病很重
But my partner, he gets very paranoid.
他認為我對此感到羞恥
He thinks I'm ashamed of
他想讓我們的關系更加公開化
He wants me to be more public about it, so
不管怎么樣 我是同性戀
Anyway, I'm gay.
謝謝
Thanks.
嗯
Yeah.
嘿 先生 不要擔心了
Hey, man, don't worry about it.
黑客們很少集中注意力 他們很快就會無聊 然后就會騷擾別的人了
Hackers have a short attention span. They'll get bored, harass someone else.
邪惡公司正在考慮 跟我們分道揚鑣
Evil Corp is thinking about leaving us.
我都不知道該不該怪他們
And I don't know if I can blame them.
他們本可以找別的安全團隊的
They could have called their other security teams.
但他們找了你
They called you.
總會有那么些人喜歡我們
Well, somebody over there likes us
但是 泰利 科爾比 他現在壓力很大
but Terry Colby, he's getting the pressure.
是他提出要離開我們的
and he calls the shots.
邪惡公司整個我們生意的80%
Evil Corp is 80% of our business.
如果我們失去了他們 將會是我們最大的損失 這將會是...
If we lose them, it's gonna be it for us.It's gonna be it...
我的損失
For me.
我覺得 我可以跟你講這些
NI feel like I can talk to you.
我的意思是 比跟別人講的更多
I mean, more than the others, anyway.
我確信 從某種程度上講 公司要是倒了 你會很高興的
I'm sure, in a weird way, you'll be happy if we went under.
別裝了
Oh, come on.
我知道你不喜歡 穿那些很蠢的襯衫
I know you hate wearing those stupid shirts.
吉迪恩?
Gideon?
我向你保證我會找到他們的
I promise I'll find them.
邪惡公司的服務器應該很快就會恢復
Evil Corp service should be back up soon enough.
我會看看那些數字文件
I'll take a look at the dat file.
等到家之后 我會問問互聯網聊天室的朋友關于F社會的事
I'll ask my IRC contacts about fsociety when I get home.
我永遠都看不到他們的名字 不會在明處看到
I've never seen their name on the boards though.
他們是新手 但是他們非常優秀
They've gotta be new, but they're good.
今夜過得很艱難吧?
Rough night?
機器人             先生
我要下車了
I'm getting off here.
我覺得你應該跟我一起走
I think you should come with me.
但前提是 你沒有刪除它
But only if you didn't delete it.
如果你刪了它 我們就沒啥可聊的了
You deleted it, we got nothing to talk about.
你在跟我說話?
Are you talking to me?
請遠離 正在關閉的門
Stand clear of the closing doors, please.
你是誰
Who are you?
我們在這里等Q號線
We gotta wait for the Q.
然后呢?
Then what?
然后我們去布魯克林
Then we're going to Brooklyn.
在科尼島附近
Out by Coney Island.
為什么? 那里有什么?
Why? What's there?
很明顯你會問一大堆問題
Obviously you're gonna ask a lot of questions.
你覺得自己在做的事兒 很奇葩 我懂
It's weird what you're doing right now, I get it.
我..我不能告訴你任何事 在我們到那兒之前
I-I can't tell you anything until we get there.
你不能在這兒抽煙
Can't smoke in here.
你一直在跟蹤我
You've been following me.
為什么?
Why?
你想從我身上得到什么?
What do you want from me?
我父親是個小偷
My dad was a petty thief.
從來不能老老實實的做一份工作 所以 他就搶劫
Never could hold down a job. So, he just robbed,
便利店啦 商店啦 小偷小摸的
convenience stores,shops,small-time stuff.
有一次他坐下來跟我說了一些話 是我終生難忘的
One time,he sat me down,he told me something I never forgot.
他說 "每個人都會偷東西
He said, "Everyone steals.
社會就是這么運作的
"That's how it works.
你覺得每個人都能得到他們應得的東西么?  不是的
"You think people out there are getting exactly What they deserve? No.
他們要么拿錢太多 要么太少
"They're getting paid over or under,
但是總有人遭到欺騙
but someone in the chain always gets bamboozled.
"我是偷東西 兒子 但是我沒有被抓 "
"I steal, Son,but I don't get caught."
那是我的社會契約
"That's my contract with society.
如果你能抓到我偷東西 那我就進監獄了
"Now if you can catch me stealing, I'll go to jail.
但是如果你不能
"But if you can't,
那我就賺到錢了"
then I've earned the money."
我很敬佩他所說的 兄弟
I respected that, man.
在我小時候我覺得那種事很酷
I thought that shit was cool as a little kid.
幾年之后
A few years after that,
他終于被抓了
they finally caught him.
幾年之后
A few years after that,
他終于被抓了
they finally caught him.
被送進了監獄并于五年之后逝世
Sent him to jail. Dies five years later.
我的崇敬也隨他而去
My respect goes with him.
我以為他在做自己的事的時候是自由的
I thought he was free doing what he did,
但事實并不是這樣的
but he wasn't.
他在監獄
He was in prison.
就像你現在一樣 伊利艾特
Just like you are now,Elliot.
但是我要把你救出來
But I'm gonna break you out.
你們為什么要碰面?
Why would you guys actually meet IRL?
你記得那個叫O-Megz的黑客團隊么?
You remember that hacker group O-Megz?
就是那個被自己的隊長舉報 導致6名黑客進監獄的那件事?
They got outed by their own leader to the FBI,and six hackers went to prison for it?
你知道他們怎么被抓的么?
You know how they got 'em?
警方黑進了一個成員的電腦
They went on the dude's computer,
通過郵件VPN對話 短信
tracked 'em all down through emails,VPN sessions,
將他們一網打盡
chat messages, texts.
- 就因為那一個人 所有的一切都泡湯了 這就叫 - 一顆老鼠屎壞了一鍋湯
- One guy, and the whole thing comes down. It's what's called - A central point of failure.
對 因為他們拒絕彼此親自見面
Right Because they refused to meet in person,
最終他們一次次發送的笑臉表情符號暴露了他們
they compromised each other every time they sent so much as a smiley face.
所以這里的規矩就是
The rule here is,
就在這兒做事
it's done here,
而且只在這兒做事
and only here.
一切終了于你走出這扇門  開始于你推門進來
It ends when you walk out that door,and begins when you walk in.
我們的加密術就是現實世界
Our encryption is the real world.
那你們之間如何交流?
How do you talk to each other then?
我們不交流
We don't.
我們時進時出 在我們有空的時候來進行這個項目
We come and go, work on the project when we can.
那你如何能夠相信他們?
How do you trust them?
我對每個人都有測試
I give them an exercise.
如果他們通過了 那就加入我們 如果他們沒通過...
If they pass, they join us. If they fail
那么昨晚的分布式拒絕服務攻擊
The DDoS attack last night,
就是你在測試我嘍
you were testing me.
你說過你們有個項目
You said there was a project.
- 是什么項目? - 那件事過會兒再議
-What's the project? -That'll come later.
我現在只是想讓你來看看這個地方
I just wanted you to see the place.
要是沒有中心處理器 你也巧婦難為無米之炊
There's not much you can do without a CPU.
我瘋了
I'm crazy.
我一定是瘋了因為剛才的一切的確是發生了 對么?
I have to be crazy because that didn't just happen, right?
這是都是幻想  這是幻想么?
This is a delusion. Is this a delusion?
該死 我有精神分裂癥了
Shit, I'm a schizo.
我這次是真的迷失了么?
Have I really lost it this time?
不 不 昨晚發生的事的確是真的
No, no. Last night happened. It was real.
安吉拉給我打電話了 我是去了全安全公司
Angela called me. I was at AllSafe.
邪惡公司的服務器的確癱瘓了
Evil Corp's servers were compromised.
那些都是事實 不是幻覺
Those are facts,not delusions
我知道的 我知道的 我知道的 我知道我是在跟一個幻想中的人在說這些事兒
I know. I know, I know I realize I'm saying all of this to an imaginary person,
但是是我創造了你
but I created you.
我可沒造這一堆破事兒
I didn't create this.
噢 還好你回來了
Oh, thank God you're here.
我正要去星巴克等你呢
I was just about to go wait in the Starbucks.
你住的這個社區很爛 你知道么?
You live in a bad neighborhood. Do you know that?
我知道
I do know that.
你想喝高點然后一起看你喜歡的電影么?
Do you want to get high and watch your favorite movie?
喔 你昨晚救了我們
Oh, you saved our asses last night
我本以為吉迪恩一定會炒了我的
I thought Gideon was definitely gonna fire me.
你去哪兒了?
Where have you been?
我以為你會在睡覺呢
I thought you'd be sleeping.
我..嗯 我在地鐵上睡著了
I--yeah, I fell asleep on the train.
這聽上去就像是謊話
That sounds like such a lie,
但是 不管怎么樣 我現在不想知道
but, whatever. I don't want to get into that right now.
所以我們到底要不要喝酒看電影??
So you want to do this?
我都想庫爾提了
I miss Qwerty.
希望她還愛我
I hope she still loves me.
見鬼
Shit.
她不該出現在這兒的 好么?
She wasn't supposed to be here, okay?
給我一分鐘我會處理掉她的
Give me a minute and I'll get rid of her.
沒事的  呃...
That's okay. Um...
這挺棒的
This is great.
- 伊利艾特 我很替你高興 - 不 事情不是這樣的
-Elliot, I'm happy for you. -No, it's not like that.
嗯 也許其實也不錯 你知道么?
Well, maybe it should be,you know?
你在約會其實...挺好的
It's good that you're...dating.
嗯 我們周一再見嘍
Well, I'll see you on Monday.
我們下次再一起看電影吧
We can do movie night next time.
我保證 好么?
I promise, okay?
嗯
Yeah.
玩的開心喲
Have fun.
嗯..伊利艾特?
Mm, Elliot?
噢 混蛋 現在已經是周三了么?
Oh, shit. Is it Wednesday?
- 夏拉 - 我得去換邊停車了
-Shayla. -I have to move my car.
夏拉 離開這里
Shayla, leave.
馬上
Now.
從來沒有關于機器人先生的信息哪里都沒有
No mention of Mr. Robot anywhere.
也沒有關于"F社會"的信息
No mention of F-society.
任何黑客論壇上都沒有
Not on any of the hacker boards.
網上交談 論壇 博客上通通沒有
Not on IRC, forums, blogs,
沒有人聽說過他們
no one's heard of them.
那片地產13年來歸開心社會娛樂有限公司所有
Property was owned by Fun Society Amusement, LLC for 13 years.
產權人在一年半前被殺了
Owner was shot a killed a year and a half ago.
自此便成為無主地
No owner since.
而且在此之前的所有權歷史信息根本不存在
And the ownership history before that is sparse to nonexistent.
這個人很強啊 相當強
This guy is good. Very good.
不管了
Doesn't matter.
他們的網絡地址都在那個數據文件里
Their arcade network's IP is in the dat file
用來舉報他們足夠了
That'll be enough to turn them in.
你有何企圖 機器人先生?
What's your ask, Mr. Robot?
嘿 兄弟
Hey, man,
你老大在哪?
where's your boss?
好吧 別說廢話
Okay, cut the bullshit.
你什么時候才能給我們根目錄的權限?
When are you going to give us access to the root directory?
什么?
What?
省省吧 老兄 我寫的那個隱匿公式
Dude, come on. I wrote that rootkit.
我還得在那個數據文件上加上科爾比的網絡地址才行
I still have to put Colby's IP in the dat file.
傻蛋
Dickhead.
伊利艾特! 好消息
Elliot! Good news.
我搶到了最后一袋超市的夾餡面包
I scored the last bag of Twinkies from Gristedes.
來一個么?
You want one?
她剛才居然叫我傻蛋
She just called me a dickhead.
嗯哼 那是戴琳
Yeah, that's Darlene.
嘿 你喜歡摩天輪么?
Hey, you like Ferris wheels?
噢 太美了
Ah, it's beautiful.
越高風景越好 你知道么?
Gets better the higher up you go, you know?
噢 我太喜歡這兒了
Oh, I love it up here.
你喜歡么?
You like it?
我來是告訴你 我要去舉報你們
I'm here to tell you I'm turning you in.
-我要給他們你們所有的信息 -讓我來告訴你 你來的真正原因
I'm giving them all the information.  -Let me tell you why you're really here.
你來這兒是因為 你感覺這個世界有什么不對
You're here because you sense something wrong with the world.
一些你無法解釋的事
Something you can't explain.
但是你知道它控制了你 和你身邊你在乎的所有人
But you know it controls you and everyone you care about.
你在說什么呢?
What are you talking about?
金錢
Money.
自從我們廢除金本位制以來  錢都不再是實體了 變成虛擬的了
Money hasn't been real since we got off the gold standard. It's become virtual.
是種軟件
Software.
這是我們這個世界運行的機制
The operating system of our world.
還有 伊利艾特 我們馬上就要
And, Elliot, we are on the verge
拿下這種虛擬現實了
of taking down this virtual reality.
想想吧
Think about it.
如果你能拿下一個企業那會是怎樣?
What if you could take down one conglomerate?
一個與世界經濟緊密相關的大企業
A conglomerate so deeply entrenched in the world's economy,
那可是大成功啊 我甚至都沒辦法描述它
that too big to fail doesn't even come close to describing it.
你想再創造一場金融危機嗎
You want to create another financial meltdown
就像我們剛剛經歷的這場 但比它還糟糕
like the one we just had,but way worse.
是啊 我又為什么想要這么做呢?
Yeah, why would I want that?
每個人都會損失他們的錢財
Everyone would lose their money.
如果我告訴你這個企業恰巧持有全球70%消費者信用行業的股份呢?哈?
What if I told you that this conglomerate just so happens to own 70% of the global consumer credit industry?
如果我們能準確地黑入他們的數據中心
If we hit their data center just right,
我們就能系統地格式化所用用戶的資料
we could systematically format all the servers
- 包括備份 - 這樣會清除掉...
-including backup. -That would erase all
我們欠的所有債
All the debt we owe them.
每一筆信用卡 貸款 抵押的記錄都會被清除
Every record of every credit card, loan, and mortgage would be wiped clean.
強化那些過時的紙質記錄是不可能的
It would be impossible to reinforce outdated paper records.
所有一切都煙消云散
It would all be gone.
人類歷史上最大的財產重新分配事件
The single biggest incident of wealth redistribution in history.
邪惡公司 你說的那個公司
Evil Corp. The conglomerate.
這就是你選我的原因啊
That's why you picked me.
因為我在全安全工作
Because I work at AllSafe.
明天 全安全將會有聯邦調查局
Tomorrow, AllSafe is going to get a visit from the FBI
和美國網絡司令部的人到訪
and the U.S. Cyber Command.
你去修改那個數字文件
You are going to modify the dat file
把科爾比的IP終端地址放進去
and put Colby's terminal IP address in there.
泰利 科爾比嗎?
Terry Colby?
你準備陷害他?
You're gonna frame him?
沒人會相信的
No one's gonna believe that.
我見過他 他就是個腦殘
I met him, he's a moron.
FBI不也是么
So are the FBI.
即使他們不相信是他做的
Even if they don't believe he did it,
他們也會相信是他幫了別人做的
they'll believehe gave someone access to it.
是啊 然后他就是會進監獄而已
Yeah, he'll just go to jail.
那有什么用啊?
What good will that do?
要扳倒一個大的企業集團是不能瞄準核心一擊斃命的
You don't take down a conglomerate by shooting them in the heart.
大企業集團就是這樣
That's the thing about conglomerates,
他們沒有核心
they don't have hearts.
要一點一點的瓦解掉
You take them down limb by limb.
隨著企業慢慢被拆散
And as they unravel,
他們一手掌控的錯覺也會瓦解
their illusion of control unravels.
你是誰?
Who are you?
你以后再知道也不遲
That'll come later.
現在 你有很多事需要好好想想
Right now, you have a lot to think about.
你得修改那個數據文件
You have to change the dat file
然后把科爾比的IP輸進去
and put Colby's IP in there.
如果你那樣做的話
You do that,
那就是發動了一場史上最大型的革命
you have set in motion the largest revolution the world will ever see.
尼爾·戴蒙德演唱 ?
Neil Diamond's ?
若你離去 ?
If you go away ?
在這夏日里 ?
On this summer day ?
不如帶著太陽 ?
Then you might as well ?
一同離去 ?
take the sun away ?
夏日天空 ?
All the birds that flew ?
鳥兒翱翔 ?
In a summer sky ?
那時我們愛如蜜糖 ?
When our love was new ?
心氣昂揚 ?
And our hearts were high ?
那時白晝伊始 ?
When the day was young ?
夜晚漫長 ?
And the night was long ?
月色靜靜 ?
And the moon stood still ?
鳥聲輕唱 ?
For the night birds song ?
若你離去 ?
If you go away ?
若你留下 ?
But if you stay ?
我會陪在你身邊 ?
I'll make you a day ?
讓你的一天 ?
Like no day's been ?
永生難忘 ?
Or will be again ?
我們在陽光下起航 ?
We'll sail on the sun ?
我們在細雨中前行 ?
We'll ride on the rain ?
我們與樹木私語 ?
We'll talk to the trees ?
我們沐浴微風 ?
And worship the wind ?
如此你仍離開 ?
Then if you go ?
我會明白 ?
I'll understand ?
留你足夠的愛 ?
Leave me just enough love ?
填滿我雙手空白 ?
To fill up my hand ?
若你離去 ?
If you go away ?
我知道你必須離去 ?
As I know you must ?
這世上我 ?
There'll be nothing left ?
生無可戀 ?
In the world to trust ?
只余房間 ?
Just an empty room ?
空蕩一片 ?
Full of empty space ?
正如我所見 ?
Like the empty look ?
你一臉茫然 ?
I see on your face ?
如今我是否可以坦白 ?
Can I tell you now ?
當你轉身離開 ?
As you turn to go ?
我將慢慢老去 ?
I'll be dying slowly ?
直到你我再次會面 ?
Till your next hello ?
若你離去 ?
If you go away ?
若你離去... ?
If you go away... ?
我該如何償還我的學生貸款？
債務奴隸 新一代美國夢
全球貧富差距值達20年來新高且仍在擴大
邪惡總會勝利
那么 我們開始吧?
So, what do we got?
你們看一下日程的第一頁
So, if you'll take a look at the first page of your agenda--
是你阻止了黑客入侵
You're the one who stopped the hack.
你們知道么 分析部的姑娘們說這次挺難搞的
You know, the gals in analysis said this was a tough one.
正常情況下
All things being equal,
這次入侵可能會讓我們當掉好多天 所以...
it should have shut us down for days, so...
干得漂亮
you did good.
恩
Okay.
我們應該先從客戶經理 安吉拉開始
We should start with our account executive, Angela.
好的 我們初次注意到被攻擊
Okay, we first noticed the breach
是在周五晚上 是東部標準時間上午兩點零七分
2:07 A.M. Eastern Standard on Friday night.
你是說周六?
You mean, Saturday?
抱歉 是的 準確的講 是周六早晨
Sorry, yes, technically, Saturday morning.
好的 安吉拉
Yeah, okay, Angela,
我們在這開會就是為了這個 準確的技術細節
that's what we're here for. The technicals.
好的
Right.
恩
Yes.
總之 他在35分的時候到達辦公室 然后我告訴
Anyway, he arrived at the office35 and I instru--
好吧 等等 停一下
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
這么說那已經是初次被攻擊之后半個小時了
So that's almost a half hour after the initial breach.
為什么沒有人用筆記本接進來?
Why didn't anyone pipe in from their laptops?
- 規定流程不是那樣的 - 那樣并不安全
- It's not protocol - It wouldn't have been secure
如果讓人通過終端登入這個
if someone terminaled in on this.
等有人過來 然后通過安全線路
It was the smarter move to have someone come in
- 登錄是更好地做法 - 正是如此
-so they can log in on a secure line. -Exactly.
- 那樣羅伊德就能 - 等 等等 打斷一下--
Then Lloyd was able to -Just--just actually, just one second.
恩
- Yeah.
你知道的 我 呃
You know, I, uh,
我一直很喜歡這里的風景
I always loved this view.
現在 既然那件事已經解決了
Now that that's taken care of,
那我們就繼續之前的話題吧
let's pick it up where we left off.
安吉拉怎么了?
What happened to Angela?
她更清楚到底發生了什么
She knows more about what happened.
她對我們不會有很有用的 起碼在這個層面不會
She's not going to work out for us, not on this level.
我們現在需要堅持從更技術的角度看
We need to stick to the more tech savvy here.
好了 咱們來討論一下這件事的核心
Now, let's get to the heart of this thing
我不能一直坐在這花上20分鐘慢慢瀏覽文件
because I can't sit hereand look through a packet for the next 20 minutes.
好了 到底是誰做的?
All right, just who did this?
就這么難?
Is it that hard?
誰做的?
Who did this?
我發現這個惡意程序配置文件的IP地址有固定的模式
I found the configuration file of the rootkit with a pattern of IP addresses.
一但能夠破譯就會知道黑客在哪里
Once you decrypt it, you'll know where the hack came from
19天
19 days.
沒有新聞 沒有拘捕 也沒有革命
No news, no arrests,no revolution
沒有FBI 科爾比和邪惡公司
No FBI, Colby, Evil Corp.
沒有機器人先生
No Mr. Robot.
沒有F社會
No fsociety.
我需要轉移一下注意力
I need to take my mind off things.
你好
Hello.
嗨 我是電子安全銀行詐騙處理部門的山姆
Hi, this is Sam from Bank of E security fraud department
很不幸地通知您 您的賬戶被盜用了
Unfortunately I have to inform you N that your account's been compromised.
什么? 怎么回事?
What? What happened?
在我回答任何問題之前 我需要核實一下您的信息
First before I can answer any questions I need to verify some information
您現在是否仍居住在霍桑大街306號？
Are you still at 306 Hawthorne Avenue?
是的 門牌號2C
Yes. Apartment 2C.
好的 您的安全問題 最喜歡的棒球隊?
Great. And your security question,favorite baseball team?
呃 洋基隊
Um, Yankees.
-我不記得有這么個安全問題啊 -最后一個問題 您的寵物叫什么?
-I don't remember this being a security question. -And lastly, your pet's name?
呃 鰭鰭
Um, Flipper.
你是誰?能說一下你的名字和號碼嗎?
Who am I speaking to?Can I get your name and number?
掌握了那些詳細信息再加上強力攻擊  我的程序大概2分鐘就可以破解他的密碼
With those details plus Na dictionary brute-force attack,it'll take my program maybe two minutes to crack his password.
我愿放棄一切只為做一個普通的人
What I wouldn't give to be normal.
生活在美好的幻想中
To live in that bubble,
天真之人的現實
the reality of the naive.
我就是這樣看待這件事的
That's how I justify this.
為了保護他們樂觀的赤子之心
To keep their optimism intact.
為了保護他們
To protect them.
怎么可能? 他年紀那么大了密碼肯定不會很復雜
How? He's too old to have a complicated password
肯定是這些信息的某種組合
It had to have been a combination of these things.
我漏掉了什么東西 我漏掉了什么東西 我漏掉了什么東西
I'm missing something,I'm missing something,I'm missing something.
邁克爾 漢森 不是他的真名
Michael Hansen N isn't his real name.
列尼 香農?
Lenny Shannon?
邁克爾 漢森?
Michael Hansen?
你今晚扮演的是哪個?
Which one are you playing tonight?
你不能繼續和克里斯塔交往了
You're going to stops eeing Krista.
搞什么鬼
What the fuck...
你要和她分手 你不會再見到她
You're going to break up with her.You're never going to see her again.
你就是那個用了我電話的家伙
You're the guy that used my phone
你劈腿你現任老婆和7個女人鬼混
You cheated on your current wife with seven different women.
我有所有的數據證明
I got digital proof of all of it.
阿什利 麥迪遜 在線招妓 假的臉書頁面
Ashley Madison, online escorts,fake Facebook pages
這些數據我都有
I own it all.
如果你不和她分手
And if you don't stop seeing her,
你妻子就會知道所有的事情 還有警察也會知道
your wife will know everything along with the police.
警察?
The police?
是啊 有一個應召女郎只有15歲
Yeah, one of the escorts was 15.
15歲的部分是我編的
That 15 part I made up,
但是他確實有偏好年輕女孩的傾向  所以幫我圓了謊
but he did have a proclivity for young escorts that helped the lie.
但是我不會那樣做的
But I'm not gonna do any of that
只要你和克里斯塔分手
as long as you break up with Krista.
今晚就分
Tonight.
成交
Done.
你還得告訴她事情的真相
You're also gonna tell her the truth.
告訴她你已經結婚了 你對自己的妻子不忠
That you're married,cheat on your wife,
花錢嫖娼
you hire hookers.
你從來沒有任何想與她認真交往的念頭
That you never had any intention of being serious with her.
為什么?
Why?
那樣會毀了她的 她以為...
That would destroy her. She thinks that...
我們是相愛的
We're in love.
正是如此 以后克里斯塔需要避開像你這種混蛋
Exactly. Krista needs to avoid dickheads like you in the future.
她探測男人的雷達需要修一修了
Her radar needs fixing.
如果你漏掉任何細節我都會知道的
I'll know if you skip any detail.
所以不要有遺漏
So don't.
還有一件事...
And one more thing...
我還需要你的一件東西
I'm gonna need something from you.
來吧
Come on.
我挺喜歡你的 鰭鰭
I like you, Flipper.
你很酷
You're cool.
我從來都不希望我的侵入是對的
I never want to be right about my hacks,
但是人們總有各種各樣的方式讓我大失所望
but people always find a way to disappoint.
邁克爾 漢森現在已經和其他人一樣被歸檔了
Michael Hansen now gets filed away among the others.
永久封存在我的數字檔案中
Forever buried in my digital cemetery.
一切幻滅的表情
The look of disillusionment.
他告訴她了 她哭了一整晚
He told her. She cried all night.
現在到了感傷的階段
Now comes the sadness.
我不喜歡看她傷心
I don't like seeing her sad.
- 你還好嗎?- 抱歉
- You okay?- Sorry.
抱歉
Sorry.
繼續吧
Go on.
我覺得安吉拉認為邪惡公司會議上發生的情況應該怪我
I think Angela blames me for what happened at the Evil Corp meeting.
我該怎么辦? 我得和她談談
What do I do? I need to talk to her.
你剛剛不是回答了自己的問題
I think you just answered your own question.
和她談談
Talk to her.
她不回我的短信或者是郵件
She won't respond to any of my texts or emails.
那就當面去找她
Then go to her in person.
告訴她你想和她談談
Tell her you need to talk
溝通是關鍵 伊利艾特
Communication is key,Elliot.
真正的人際互動
Real human interaction.
這才是現在對你來說真正重要的
That's what's important for you right now.
嘿 你 你覺得我們現在能談談嗎?
Hey. Do you-- Do you think we can talk?
什么?
- What?
你不愿跟我說話
You won't talk to me.
自從開完會之后 你就沒和我說過話
You haven't talked to mes ince the meeting.
我不想和你說話 因為我覺得很尷尬
I don't want to talk to you because I feel embarrassed
每當我一想起所發生的事情
every time I think about what happened.
行了嗎?
Okay?
沒事的 我會克服的
It's fine. I'll get over it.
- 都三個禮拜了 - 我得繼續工作了
- It's been three weeks. - I have to get back to work.
- 你就準備這樣無視我? - 你在會上的時候不必幫我說話的
You're just going to ignore me? -You didn't have to stick up for me in there
我知道你僅僅是想幫我
I know that you were just trying to help,
不過不要再那樣做了
just don't do it again.
即使我撐不下去了
Even if I'm losing.
那就讓我輸了吧 好嗎?
Let me lose, okay?
不要露出迷茫的表情
Don't look confused.
答應就好了
Just say it.
說"好的"
"Okay."
好的
Okay.
伊利艾特
Elliott.
FBI特工稱科爾比不是雇傭了黑客組織就是與其合作
FBI agents claim that Colby either used hacking groups or worked in conjunction with them
泰利 科爾比被拘留
以在合同談判階段向邪惡公司施加壓力
to pressure Evil Corp during his contract negotiations.
經過漫長而詳盡的調查 FBI方已掌握證據
After a long and exhaustive investigation,sources close to the FBI
證明黑客入侵事件與科爾比的終端有部分關聯
have confirmed the hacks were in part tied to Colby's terminal.
發生了 發生了 發生了 發生了
It's happening, it's happening,it's happening, it's happening.
it's happening, it's happening. It's happening, it's happening,
先生 請上車
Sir, step inside the car.
先生 Sir.
現在就上車
Step insidethe vehicle now.
請吧
Go ahead.
先生 請
Sir, go on in.
先生 請進去
晚上好 伊利艾特
Bon soir, Elliot.
拜托請告訴我你也看到了這個
Please tell me you're seeing this, too.
本字幕由大家字幕組原創翻譯
僅供學習使用 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
彼以國士待我 我以國士待之 用過免費優質字幕服務
而又有能力的人 有義務將這個免費服務做下去 若有心加入我們
請聯系QQ群：428872140